Alizé Debray

Web developer / Certified project manager

Work experience

2016 - 2017 5 months

• Front-end developer | The New Luncher

♥ SINGAPORE

The New Luncher is a service which allows parents to provide lunch boxes to their children at school.

- > Participated in the launch of the startup
- > Designed and developed an AngularJS web application
- > Conceived a user experience in accordance with the brand's image

2016 7 months

• Front-end development intern | SeeChic

SINGAPORE

SeeChic is an online contact lenses and sunglasses retail startup.

- > Participated in the redesign of the whole website
- > Design and developed the front-end part of a new interface
- > Managed the content's production
- > Set up an automatic emailing engine

2015 - 2016 3 months

• Salesperson | IKEA

Q Lille, FRANCE

IKEA is the world's largest furniture retailer.

- > Advised clients
- > Organised and replenished the home textiles department

2015 3 months

Front-end development intern | Orange

Q Lille, FRANCE

Orange is the French leader in telecommunications.

- > Participated in the improvement of the administration of professional clients
- > Developed the front-end part of an interface

2015 5 months

• Web development volunteer | Com&Web

Q Lille, FRANCE

Com&Web is a charity that sells websites and communication supports to collect money for the underprivileged.

> Designed and developed 6-pages showcase websites

2014 2 months

Sales intern | Darty

Q Coignières, FRANCE

Darty is the French leading household appliance store chain.

- > Pursued a sales methods training
- > Advised clients
- > Organised and replenished the small appliance department

2013 5 months

Mystery customer | Orphée

Suresnes, FRANCE

Orphée is a company specialised in the assessment of user experience.

> Evaluated customer service within a long-term study concerning one of the French leading car dealers

Education

2013 - 2018 • Engineering master's degree | Iteem - Centrale Lille 🔾 Lille, FRANCE

Preparing a master's degree in industrial and entrepreneurial engineering.

2017 - 2018 • Management master's degree | Skema Q Lille, FRANCE

Preparing a master's degree in project and program management & business development.

References



Souad-Marie Eudes Assaad

Technical specialist, Google Tel.: +65 8650 3827 souad.eudes@gmail.com



Fabrice Demarest

Project manager, Orange
Tel.: +33 (0)3 28 39 00 71
fabrice.demarest@orange.com



contact@alizedebray.com

+33 (0)6 76 67 05 04



alizedebray



alizedebray.com

Profile

As a last-year student at Iteem, the only school in France created by an engineering school in partnership with a business school, I had the chance during the last five years to take both technical and commercial courses. Thanks to the various internships that I have done, I found out that my vocation is the digital field where I continue to take advantage of this interdisciplinary approach by addressing my work with an extensive business vision. A true source of proposals, I will work autonomously, alone or within a team, to bring the best to your business.

Certifications

PRINCE2 ® Foundation AgilePM ® Foundation GPM-B ®

Technical Skills

Web

Bootstrap 4 jQuery Sass Angular 4 Php Python 3

CAD

Catia OnShape

Soft skills

Ambitious Resourceful Curious Organised

Languages

French Mother tongue
English Advanced (C1)
Spanish Intermediate (B1)

Interests







Health Sustainability

Crafts